Guide to the Committee of 100 on the Federal City records [Part I], 1932-2003 MS2017
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Subject/Issues files, 1954-1998; MS2017 Series 6
  - Historic Preservation: General - Virginia Related, 1993-1994; Series 6 (Box 63, Folder 33)
  - Historic Preservation: Org. Afro-Amer. Inst. For Historic Preservation, 1991; Series 6 (Box 63, Folder 34)
  - Historic Preservation: Army Historical Society, 1996; Series 6 (Box 63, Folder 35)
  - Historic Preservation Org - Capitol Hill, 1991; Series 6 (Box 63, Folder 36)
  - Cleveland Park Historical Society, 1994; Series 6 (Box 63, Folder 37)
  - D.C. Alliance for Preservation, 1989-1990; Series 6 (Box 63, Folder 38)
  - D.C. Historic Preservation Review Board, 1991-1995; Series 6 (Box 63, Folder 39)
  - Historic Preservation - Org: DC Preservation League, 1984-1996; Series 6 (Box 63, Folder 40)
  - Historic Preservation: Org. Historic American Bldg Survey, 1990; Series 6 (Box 63, Folder 41)
  - Org. Treasure Historic Society, 1995; Series 6 (Box 63, Folder 42)
  - Historic Preservation: Barney Circle Chron File (1 of 2), 1984-1998; Series 6 (Box 63, Folder 43)
  - Historic Preservation: Barney Circle Chron File (2 of 2), 1983-1993; Series 6 (Box 63, Folder 44)
  - Historic Preservation: Barney Circle Court Related, 1993-1995; Series 6 (Box 63, Folder 45)
  - Historic Preservation: Barney Circle - General (A), 1988-1993; Series 6 (Box 63, Folder 46)
  - Historic Preservation - Barney Circle - General (B), 1985-1996; Series 6 (Box 63, Folder 47)
  - Historic Preservation: Barney Circle Press, 1993-1994; Series 6 (Box 63, Folder 48)
  - Historic Presrvation: 14th Street Historic District, 1994-1994; Series 6 (Box 63, Folder 49)
  - Historic Presrvation: Lafayette Square, 1983-1994; Series 6 (Box 63, Folder 50)
  - Historic Preservation: L'Enfant Plan, 1984-1995; Series 6 (Box 63, Folder 51)
  - Correspondence - Shaw neighborhood, 1996; Series 6 (Box 63, Folder 52)
  - St. Elizabeth's, 1989-1996; Series 6 (Box 63, Folder 53)
  - The Committee of 100 on the Federal City: Its History and Its Service to the Nation's Capital, undated; Series 6 (Box 63, Folder 54)
  - Historical Preservation St. Elizabeth (1 of 2), 1993-1995; Series 6 (Box 64, Folder 1)
    Separated Materials
    There is one folder labeled "Historic Preservation: St. Elizabeth's 1 of 2" but no folder labeled "2 of 2." This folder may have been separated.
  - Historic Preservation: Warder-Totten House, 1995; Series 6 (Box 64, Folder 2)
  - Historic Preservation: Wilson Building, 1995-1996; Series 6 (Box 64, Folder 3)
  - Housing Committee Reports, undated; Series 6 (Box 64, Folder 4)
  - Housing: Misc. Reference, 1989-1995; Series 6 (Box 64, Folder 5)
  - Housing: DC-Home, 1987-1991; Series 6 (Box 64, Folder 6)
  - Housing and Economic Development Housing Authority, 1995-1996; Series 6 (Box 64, Folder 7)
  - Housing: Downtown Housing Requirement comp Plan, 1991-1994; Series 6 (Box 64, Folder 8)
  - Housing Code Guide DC, undated; Series 6 (Box 64, Folder 9)
  - Housing: Pennsylvania Quarter, 1991-1992; Series 6 (Box 64, Folder 10)
  - NARC Administration, 1998; Series 6; There is a CD in this folder. (Box 64, Folder 11)
  - Housing - Whitelaw Hotel, 1992; Series 6 (Box 64, Folder 12)
  - NARC, April 13, 1998; Series 6 (Box 64, Folder 13)
  - Directory of Regional Councils in the United States, 1996; Series 6 (Box 64, Folder 14)
  - The Regionalist: Special Issue, 1997; Series 6 (Box 64, Folder 15)
  - Directory of Regional Councils in the U.S., 1997; Series 6 (Box 64, Folder 16)
  - Directory of Regional Councils in the United States, 1998; Series 6 (Box 64, Folder 17)
  - NARC, 1998; Series 6 (Box 64, Folder 18)
  - Convention Center Finances, 1995-1997; Series 6 (Box 64, Folder 19)
  - Planning: Arena Testimony, October 6, 1995; Series 6 (Box 64, Folder 20)
  - Planning: Arena Testimony, October 2, 1995; Series 6 (Box 64, Folder 21)
  - Planning Arena Testimony, 1994 July 15; Series 6 (Box 64, Folder 29)
  - Arenea TF Final Report, 1995; Series 6 (Box 64, Folder 22)
  - Planning: Arena Testimony, July 28, 1995; Series 6 (Box 64, Folder 23)
  - Heritage in Jeopardy, 1987; Series 6 (Box 64, Folder 24)
  - Planning: Stadium Alternative Plans, undated; Series 6 (Box 64, Folder 25)
  - Arena Planning, 1996; Series 6 (Box 64, Folder 26)
  - Square 456, 1991-1992; Series 6 (Box 64, Folder 27)
  - Gallery Place Project (RLA), 1986-1990; Series 6 (Box 64, Folder 28)
  - Planning Arena Testimony, 1995 July 10; Series 6 (Box 64, Folder 30)
  - Planning: Arena, 1995 April 24; Series 6 (Box 64, Folder 31)
  - Planning: Arena Testimony, 1995 April 28; Series 6 (Box 64, Folder 32)
  - Planning: Arena Testimony, 1995 February 13; Series 6 (Box 64, Folder 33)
  - Planning: Arena Testimony, 1995 July 17; Series 6 (Box 64, Folder 34)
  - Planning: Arena Testimony, 1995 January 25; Series 6 (Box 64, Folder 35)
  - The D.C. Agenda Project (1 of 2), 1995-1996; Series 6 (Box 64, Folder 36)
  - The D.C. Agenda Project (2 of 2), 1995; Series 6 (Box 64, Folder 37)
  - D.C. Agenda Project: Greater Washington Research Center, 1994; Series 6 (Box 64, Folder 38)
  - D.C. Agenda Project: McKinsey Report, 1994; Series 6 (Box 64, Folder 39)
  - Public Attitudes Toward Issues Facing Washington, D.C., 1994; Series 6 (Box 64, Folder 40)
  - Housing and Urban Affairs, 1996; Series 6 (Box 64, Folder 41)
  - Planning D.C. Comp Plan Amendments, 1984-1996; Series 6 (Box 64, Folder 42)
  - Zoning: Tolling Limits, Circa 1980s-1990s; Series 6 (Box 65, Folder 1)
  - Zoning: General -, Circa 1980s-1990s; Series 6 (Box 65, Folder 2)
  - Zoning: General - Vesting Rights, Circa 1980s-1990s; Series 6 (Box 65, Folder 3)
  - Zoning Org: D.C. Zoning Commission, Circa 1980s-1990s; Series 6 (Box 65, Folder 4)
  - Zoning: Org - Midway Civic Association, Circa 1980s-1990s; Series 6 (Box 65, Folder 5)
  - Zoning: American Univ_Law School, Circa 1980s-1990s; Series 6 (Box 65, Folder 6)
  - Zoning: 1328 G Street, Circa 1980s-1990s; Series 6 (Box 65, Folder 7)
  - Zoning: Georgetown University File 1, Circa 1980s-1990s; Series 6 (Box 65, Folder 8)
  - Zoning: Georgetown University File 1A, Circa 1980s-1990s; Series 6 (Box 65, Folder 9)
  - Zoning: Georgetown University File 2, 1990; Series 6 (Box 65, Folder 10)
  - Zoning: 1201 K Street, Circa 1980s-1990s; Series 6 (Box 65, Folder 11)
  - Zoning: 1331 L Street, Circa 1980s-1990s; Series 6 (Box 65, Folder 12)
  - Zoning:1212 Massachusetts Avenue (PUD), Circa 1980s-1990s; Series 6 (Box 65, Folder 13)
  - Zoning: Petition, Circa 1980s-1990s; Series 6 (Box 65, Folder 14)
  - Zoning: New York Avenue, Circa 1980s-1990s; Series 6 (Box 65, Folder 15)
  - Zoning: Techworld, Circa 1980s-1990s; Series 6 (Box 65, Folder 16)
  - Zoning: Thomas House Area (PUD), Circa 1980s-1990s; Series 6 (Box 65, Folder 17)
  - Zoing: Wilkes Artis, Circa 1980s-1990s; Series 6 (Box 65, Folder 18)
  - Zoning: General - Misc., Circa 1980s-1990s; Series 6 (Box 65, Folder 19)
  - Zoning: General - Noise Control, Circa 1980s-1990s; Series 6 (Box 65, Folder 20)
  - Zoning: General - Property Rights, Circa 1980s-1990s; Series 6 (Box 65, Folder 21)
  - Zoning: General - PUDs, Circa 1980s-1990s; Series 6 (Box 65, Folder 22)
  - Zoning: PUD Regulations, Circa 1980s-1990s; Series 6 (Box 65, Folder 23)
  - Zoning: General - Nuisance Control, Circa 1970s-1990s; Series 6 (Box 65, Folder 24)
  - Zoning: General - Parking and Loading Requirements, Circa 1980s-1990s; Series 6 (Box 65, Folder 25)
  - Zoning: General - Regulation, Circa 1980s-1990s; Series 6 (Box 65, Folder 26)
  - Zoning: General - Retail Requirements, Circa 1980s-1990s; Series 6 (Box 65, Folder 27)
  - Zoning: General - Street Renamings, Circa 1980s-1990s; Series 6 (Box 65, Folder 28)
  - Zoning: General - Takings, Circa 1980s-1990s; Series 6 (Box 65, Folder 29)
  - Zoning: Theoretical Building Lots, Circa 1980s-1990s; Series 6 (Box 65, Folder 30)
  - Zoning Actions of the Committee of 100, Circa 1980s-1990s; Series 6 (Box 65, Folder 31)
  - Zoning: General - Air Rights, Circa 1980s-1990s; Series 6 (Box 65, Folder 32)
  - Zoning: General - Alley Closings, Circa 1980s-1990s; Series 6 (Box 65, Folder 33)
  - Zoning: General - Anacostia, Circa 1980s-1990s; Series 6 (Box 65, Folder 34)
  - Bldg Lot Control, Circa 1980s-1990s; Series 6 (Box 65, Folder 35)
  - Zoning: General - Chanceries, Circa 1980s-1990s; Series 6 (Box 65, Folder 36)
  - Zoning: General - Condemnation, Circa 1980s-1990s; Series 6 (Box 65, Folder 37)
  - Zoning: General - Foreign Misisons Act, Circa 1980s-1990s; Series 6 (Box 65, Folder 38)
  - Zoning: General - Building Heights Act, Circa 1980s-1990s; Series 6 (Box 65, Folder 39)
  - Communication Towers, Circa 1980s-1990s; Series 6 (Box 65, Folder 40)
  - Height Limitation, Circa 1980s-1990s; Series 6 (Box 65, Folder 41)
  - Building Height Act of 1910 (1 of 2), Circa 1980s-1990s; Series 6 (Box 65, Folder 42)
  - Building Height Act of 1910 (2 of 2), Circa 1980s-1990s; Series 6 (Box 65, Folder 43)
  - Height Act Reform Legislation, 1993; Series 6 (Box 65, Folder 44)
  - Transportation: Whitehurst - Status Report, September 1993; Series 6 (Box 65, Folder 45)
  - Transportation: Whitehurst - Special References, Circa 1980s-1990s; Series 6 (Box 65, Folder 46)
  - Transportation: Whitehurst - Press, Circa 1980s-1990s; Series 6 (Box 65, Folder 47)
  - Transportation: Whitehurst - Testimony, September 1993; Series 6 (Box 65, Folder 48)
  - Transportation: Whitehurst - Plan C100, Circa 1980s-1990s; Series 6 (Box 65, Folder 49)
  - Transportation: Whitehurst - EIS 2 of 3, Circa 1980s-1990s; Series 6 (Box 65, Folder 50)
    Related Materials
    File "Transportation: Whitehurst - EIS 1 of 3" is in box 67
  - Transportation: Whitehurst - EIS 3 of 3, Circa 1980s-1990s; Series 6 (Box 65, Folder 51)
    File "Transportation: Whitehurst - EIS 1 of 3," is in box 67
  - DCM C100 Expenses, Circa 1980s-1990s; Series 6 (Box 66, Folder 1)
  - Curriculum Vitae, Circa 1980s-1990s; Series 6 (Box 66, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, Circa 1980s-1990s; Series 6 (Box 66, Folder 3)
  - Committee Notes and Organizational Documents, Circa 1980s-1990s; Series 6 (Box 66, Folder 4)
  - Draft Letter to President Clinton concerning monumental plan, Circa 1980s-1990s; Series 6 (Box 66, Folder 5)
  - Pages for the Arts Magazine, Circa 1980s-1990s; Series 6 (Box 66, Folder 6)
  - The National Capital Planning Commission (NCPC), Circa 1980s-1990s; Series 6 (Box 66, Folder 7)
  - Newspaper articles and newsletters, Circa 1980s-1990s; Series 6 (Box 66, Folder 8)
  - Committee of 100, 1989; Series 6 (Box 66, Folder 9)
  - Planning: Nelson Paper - "Regional Pln. Alt.", Circa 1980s-1990s; Series 6 (Box 66, Folder 10)
  - Planning: Opera House, Circa 1980s-1990s; Series 6 (Box 66, Folder 11)
  - Metro of Washington Post - Fairfax, VA, Circa 1980s-1990s; Series 6 (Box 66, Folder 12)
  - Planning: Red Cross Building - 1 of 3, Circa 1980s-1990s; Series 6 (Box 66, Folder 13)
  - Planning: Red Cross Building - 2 of 3, Circa 1980s-1990s; Series 6 (Box 66, Folder 14)
  - Planning: Red Cross Building - 3 of 3, Circa 1980s-1990s; Series 6 (Box 66, Folder 15)
  - Planning: Monumental Core 1st initiatives, Circa 1980s-1990s; Series 6 (Box 66, Folder 16)
  - Planning: Monumental core HR (House of Representatives Concurrent Resolution) 196, Circa 1980s-1990s; Series 6 (Box 66, Folder 17)
  - Monumental Core: McGrath Statement 1996, Series 6 (Box 66, Folder 18)
  - Planning: Monumental Core - Plans and Presentation Materials (1 of 2), Circa 1980s-1990s; Series 6 (Box 66, Folder 19)
  - Planning: Monumental Core - Plans and Presentation Materials (2 of 2), Circa 1980s-1990s; Series 6 (Box 66, Folder 20)
  - Planning: Monumental Core Press, Circa 1980s-1990s; Series 6 (Box 66, Folder 21)
  - Planning: Monumental Core - Transcript NCPC C100, 1994 June 02; Series 6 (Box 66, Folder 22)
  - Planning: Museum of Health and Medicine, Circa 1980s-1990s; Series 6 (Box 66, Folder 23)
  - Pennsylvania Avenue Closing, 1995 June 16; Series 6 (Box 66, Folder 24)
  - Planning: GSA Comp Plan, Circa 1980s-1990s; Series 6 (Box 66, Folder 25)
  - Planning: Monumental Core - Core Newsletter, Circa 1980s-1990s; Series 6 (Box 66, Folder 26)
  - Planning: Monumental Core Correspondence, Circa 1980s-1990s; Series 6 (Box 66, Folder 27)
  - Staff Draft: Comprehensive Plan for the National Capital, 1992 September 01; Series 6 (Box 66, Folder 28)
  - Planning: D.C. Comprehensive Plan -NCPC Elements, Circa 1980s-1990s; Series 6 (Box 66, Folder 29)
  - Planning: D.C. Comprehensive Plan - General 1, Circa 1980s-1990s; Series 6 (Box 66, Folder 30)
  - Planning: D.C. Comprehensive Plan General 2, Circa 1980s-1990s; Series 6 (Box 66, Folder 31)
  - Planning: D.C. Comprehensive Plan - General 3, Circa 1980s-1990s; Series 6 (Box 66, Folder 32)
  - Planning: D.C. Comp Plan - Downtown Plan, Circa 1980s-1990s; Series 6 (Box 67, Folder 1)
  - Committee of 100, 1987; Series 6 (Box 67, Folder 2)
  - Committee of 100, 1988; Series 6 (Box 67, Folder 3)
  - World War II Memorial, 1997; Series 6 (Box 67, Folder 4)
  - C100 (1 of 2), 1994; Series 6 (Box 67, Folder 5)
  - C100 (2 of 2), 1994; Series 6 (Box 67, Folder 5a)
  - Transportation: General Forecasts, Circa 1980s-1990s; Series 6 (Box 67, Folder 6)
  - Transportation: General Committee Reports, misc., Circa 1980s-1990s; Series 6 (Box 67, Folder 7)
  - Transportation: General - Miscellaneous Reference, Circa 1980s-1990s; Series 6 (Box 67, Folder 8)
  - Committee of 100 Transportation Committee, Circa 1980s-1990s; Series 6 (Box 67, Folder 9)
  - Transportation: Streets and Alleys, Circa 1980s-1990s; Series 6 (Box 67, Folder 10)
  - Transportation: Cog Transportation Board, Circa 1980s-1990s; Series 6 (Box 67, Folder 11)
  - Transportation: Canal Road, Circa 1980s-1990s; Series 6 (Box 67, Folder 12)
  - Mapping the Future of Transportation in DC_x000D_, 1988-02-01T00:00:00+00:00; Series 6 (Box 67, Folder 13)
  - Water Resources: Anacostia / Bladensburg, Circa 1980s-1990s; Series 6 (Box 67, Folder 14)
  - Transportation: Whitehurst Chron A, Circa 1980s-1990s; Series 6 (Box 67, Folder 15)
  - Transportation: Whitehurst Chron B, Circa 1980s-1990s; Series 6 (Box 67, Folder 16)
  - Transportation: Whitehurst Correspondence and Memos, Circa 1980s-1990s; Series 6 (Box 67, Folder 17)
  - Transportation: Whitehurst - EIS 1 of 3, Circa 1980s-1990s; Series 6 (Box 67, Folder 18)
    Files "Transportation: Whitehurst - EIS 2 of 3" and "Transportation: Whitehurst - EIS 3 of 3" are in box 65
- Oversized records, 1967-1986; MS2017 Series 7
  This series contains publications, blueprints, and maps. This material dates from 1967-86. These documents relate to city planning and transportation such as inter-state highway issues. The blueprints are of the Federal Triangle area and the remodeling of the City Post Office.
  - Completing the National System of Interstate and Defense Highways, 1967 (Box 51, Folder 1)
  - Master Plan for the Federal Triangle, 1982 (Box 51, Folder 2)
  - NCPC-"Federal Capital Improvements Program," FY, 1981-1986 (Box 51, Folder 3)
  - NCPC- "Shoreline Acquisition and Development Policies and Programs,", 1976 (Box 51, Folder 4)
  - Blueprints for Postal Square and the City Post Office, 1988 (Box 52A, Oversize-folder 1)
  - Blueprints for Federal and District Owned Reservations in D.C., 1973 (Box 52A, Oversize-folder 2)
- Accession 2011.068, 1957-2003; Series 8; 16.5 Linear Feet 11 record cartons
  Currently arranged in original order of donation.
  This series has not yet been integrated with the previous donation. The type of records match all the previous 7 series and should at some point to integrated.
  Scope and Contents
  This series contains correspondence, publicity, and planning documentation. The topics in this series conver all the topics of the previous seven series. There is data related to the work of the Committee of 100 regarding fundraising, politics, transportation, urban planning and publicity. These materials date from 1957-2003.
  Immediate Source of Acquisition
  Gift of Committee of 100, October 5, 2011 (2011.068).
  - PLANNING: ARENA ARENA TAX, 1995; Series 8 (Box 52, Folder 1)
  - PLANNING: ARENA COMMISSION OF FINE ARTS, 1995; Series 8 (Box 52, Folder 2)
  - PLANNING: ARENA CPC, 1995; Series 8 (Box 52, Folder 3)
  - PLANNING: ARENA DC CONVENTION CENTER, 1995; Series 8 (Box 52, Folder 4)
  - PLANNING: ARENA CORRESPONDENCE, 1995; Series 8 (Box 52, Folder 5)
  - PLANNING: ARENA DC COUNCIL ACTION, 1995; Series 8 (Box 52, Folder 6)
  - PLANNING: ARENA DC PRESERVATION LEAGUE, 1995; Series 8 (Box 52, Folder 7)
  - PLANNING: ARENA DOWNTOWN URBAN RENEWAL, 1995; Series 8 (Box 52, Folder 8)
  - PLANNING: ARENA ENVIRONMENTAL IMPACT STATEMENT, 1995; Series 8 (Box 52, Folder 9)
  - PLANNING: ARENA G STREET CLOSING, 1995; Series 8 (Box 52, Folder 10)
  - PLANNING: ARENA HEARING, 1995 January 9; Series 8 (Box 52, Folder 11)
  - PLANNING: ARENA HEARING, 1995 Septemer 8; Series 8 (Box 52, Folder 12)
  - PLANNING: ARENA HGSD ARENA FAB, 1995 April 11; Series 8 (Box 52, Folder 13)
  - PLANNING: ARENA DC COUNCIL ACTION 2, 1995; Series 8 (Box 52, Folder 14)
  - PLANNING: ARENA LIBRARY ITEMS TO CHECK, 1995; Series 8 (Box 52, Folder 15)
  - PLANNING: ARENA MEMORANDUM OF AGREEMENT, 1995; Series 8 (Box 52, Folder 16)
  - PLANNING: ARENA PHOTOGRAPHS, 1995; Series 8 (Box 52, Folder 17)
  - PLANNING: ARENA REPORT, 1995 March 22; Series 8 (Box 52, Folder 18)
  - PLANNING: ARENA TIME SHEETS MISCELLANEOUS, 1995; Series 8 (Box 52, Folder 19)
  - PLANNING: ARENA SITE PLANS, 1995; Series 8 (Box 52, Folder 20)
  - PLANNING: ARENA SMITHSONIAN, 1995; Series 8 (Box 52, Folder 21)
  - PLANNING: ARENA SPORTS ARENA FORUM, 1995; Series 8 (Box 52, Folder 22)
  - PLANNING: ARENA PRESS CITY PAPER ARTICLE, 1995; Series 8 (Box 52, Folder 23)
  - PLANNING: ARENA SUBCOMMITTEE ON TRANSPORTATION, 1995; Series 8 (Box 52, Folder 24)
  - PLANNING: ARENA SUBCOMMITTEE ON DESIGN, 1995; Series 8 (Box 52, Folder 25)
  - PLANNING: ARENA PRESS/2, 1995; Series 8 (Box 52, Folder 26)
  - PLANNING: ARENA PRESS 1/2, 1995; Series 8 (Box 52, Folder 27)
  - PLANNING: ARENA NATIONAL CAPITAL PLANNING COMMISSION, 1995; Series 8 (Box 52, Folder 28)
  - TRUSTEES MEETING MINUTES, 1979-1993; Series 8 (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - LETTER TO PRESIDENT REAGAN RE APPT TO CFC, 1985 April 17; Series 8 (Box 53, Folder 2)
  - MEMBERSHIP MEETING MINUTES, 1967 March - 1995 October; Series 8 (Box 53, Folder 3)
  - DOWNTOWN PLAN, 1980; Series 8 (Box 53, Folder 4)
  - TRUSTEES MEETING MINUTES, 1983 January 13-1996 May 9; Series 8 (Box 53, Folder 5)
  - TECHWORLD, undated; Series 8 (Box 53, Folder 6)
  - RFK STADIUM, undated; Series 8 (Box 53, Folder 7)
  - DC PRISON, undated; Series 8 (Box 53, Folder 8)
  - PUBLICITY, 1989; Series 8 (Box 53, Folder 9)
  - PORTALS, undated; Series 8 (Box 53, Folder 10)
  - TENLEY AND CLEVELAND PARK EMERGENCY COMMITTEE V. D.C., 1988 November 17; Series 8 (Box 53, Folder 11)
  - ZONING, undated; Series 8 (Box 53, Folder 12)
  - WATER RESOURCES, undated; Series 8 (Box 53, Folder 13)
  - WASHINGTON COMMITTEE, undated; Series 8 (Box 53, Folder 14)
  - WASHINGTON TIMES, undated; Series 8 (Box 53, Folder 15)
  - WARD PLANNING, undated; Series 8 (Box 53, Folder 16)
  - TREES (DC), undated; Series 8 (Box 53, Folder 17)
  - TRANSPORTATION ISSUES, 1985-1992; Series 8 (Box 53, Folder 18)
  - FOREIGN MISSIONS BILL, undated; Series 8 (Box 53, Folder 19)
  - FINE ARTS COMMISSION, undated; Series 8 (Box 53, Folder 20)
  - CITY PAPER ARTICLE ON HEIGHT OF BUILDINGS ACT, 1990 January 05; Series 8 (Box 53, Folder 21)
  - INTERNAL REVENUE SERVICE, 1970 November 27; Series 8 (Box 53, Folder 22)
  - BETTY ANN KANE, 1982; Series 8 (Box 53, Folder 23)
  - MASON'S NECK, 1966, 1983; Series 8 (Box 53, Folder 24)
  - NATIONAL CAPITAL PLANNING COMMISSION, 1987-1994; Series 8 (Box 53, Folder 25)
  - NOMINATIONS FOR TRUSTEES, 1981-1990; Series 8 (Box 53, Folder 26)
  - NORTHERN VA CONSERVATION COUNCIL, 1986-1989; Series 8 (Box 53, Folder 27)
  - COMMITTEE -- ORGANIZATION, STRUCTURE, ETC., undated; Series 8 (Box 53, Folder 28)
  - PARKS, undated; Series 8 (Box 53, Folder 29)
  - PIPA ACCOUNTS -- CORRESPONDENCE, 1986-1994; Series 8 (Box 53, Folder 30)
  - PLANNING AND URBAN, 1980-1988; Series 8 (Box 53, Folder 31)
  - BYLAWS, 1990 December 31; Series 8 (Box 53, Folder 32)
  - CITIZENS PLANNING COALITION, 1984-1985; Series 8 (Box 53, Folder 33)
  - COUNCIL OF GOVERNMENTS, 1981-1984; Series 8 (Box 53, Folder 34)
  - COLUMBIA HISTORICAL SOCIETY, 1984-1986; Series 8 (Box 53, Folder 35)
  - COST TO CONSUMERS, 1989; Series 8 (Box 53, Folder 36)
  - COMTE FOR PRESERVING THE POTOMAC - MERRYWOOD APARTMENTS, 1962; Series 8 (Box 53, Folder 37)
  - ADMINISTRATIVE, undated; Series 8 (Box 53, Folder 38)
  - AMERICAN PLANNING ASSOCIATION, 1990-1991; Series 8 (Box 53, Folder 39)
  - ANACOSTIA, undated; Series 8 (Box 53, Folder 40)
  - DIXON/BARRY MAYOR - CORRESPONDENCE, 1984-1988; Series 8 (Box 53, Folder 41)
  - BIOGRAPHIES, 1980-1990; Series 8 (Box 53, Folder 42)
  - ST. PATRICKS/CARROLL SQUARE 1, 1999; Series 8 (Box 54, Folder 1)
  - ST. PATRICKS/CARROLL SQUARE 2, 1999; Series 8 (Box 54, Folder 2)
  - ST. PATRICKS/CARROLL SQUARE 3, 1999; Series 8 (Box 54, Folder 3)
  - ST. PATRICKS/CARROLL SQUARE 4, 1999; Series 8 (Box 54, Folder 4)
  - STATUS OF GRANT SEEKING, undated; Series 8 (Box 55, Folder 1)
  - FOUNDATIONS FILE LIST, undated; Series 8 (Box 55, Folder 2)
  - PROPOSALS STANDARD ATTACHMENTS, undated; Series 8 (Box 55, Folder 3)
  - PROPOSALS, 2002-2003; Series 8 (Box 55, Folder 4)
  - HERBERT BLOCK FOUNDATION, undated; Series 8 (Box 55, Folder 5)
  - CAFRITZ FOUNDATION, undated; Series 8 (Box 55, Folder 6)
  - COMMUNITY FOUNDATION NATIONAL CAPITAL REGION, undated; Series 8 (Box 55, Folder 7)
  - DREYFUS FOUNDATION, 1999-2001; Series 8 (Box 55, Folder 8)
  - THE DUNN FOUNDATION, undated; Series 8 (Box 55, Folder 9)
  - ENGLAND FAMILY FOUNDATION, undated; Series 8 (Box 55, Folder 10)
  - THE ENTERPRISE FOUNDATION, undated; Series 8 (Box 55, Folder 11)
  - JOHN FOWLER FOUNDATION, undated; Series 8 (Box 55, Folder 12)
  - THE FREEDOM FORUM, undated; Series 8 (Box 55, Folder 13)
  - CARL M FREEMAN FOUNDATION, undated; Series 8 (Box 55, Folder 14)
  - PHILLIP L GRAHAM FOUNDATION, undated; Series 8 (Box 55, Folder 15)
  - KIPLINGER FOUNDATION, undated; Series 8 (Box 55, Folder 16)
  - KRESGE FOUNDATION, undated; Series 8 (Box 55, Folder 17)
  - LAWRENCE FOUNDATION, undated; Series 8 (Box 55, Folder 18)
  - HELEN SPERRY LEA, undated; Series 8 (Box 55, Folder 19)
  - MARPAT FOUNDATION, undated; Series 8 (Box 55, Folder 20)
  - MEYER FOUNDATION, undated; Series 8 (Box 55, Folder 21)
  - MCGOWAN FUND, undated; Series 8 (Box 55, Folder 22)
  - MILLER AND CHEVALIER FOUNDATION, undated; Series 8 (Box 55, Folder 23)
  - NATIONAL TRUST FOR HISTORIC PRESERVATION, undated; Series 8 (Box 55, Folder 24)
  - PRINCE CHARITABLE TRUSTS, undated; Series 8 (Box 55, Folder 25)
  - SPRINGER-LANG FOUNDATION, undated; Series 8 (Box 55, Folder 26)
  - PUBLIC WELFARE FOUNDATION, undated; Series 8 (Box 55, Folder 27)
  - SPRING CREEK FOUNDATION, undated; Series 8 (Box 55, Folder 28)
  - SUMMIT FUND, undated; Series 8 (Box 55, Folder 29)
  - TRELLIS FUND, undated; Series 8 (Box 55, Folder 30)
  - FUNDRAISING GENERAL, undated; Series 8 (Box 55, Folder 31)
  - FOUNDATION CORRESPONDENCE, undated; Series 8 (Box 55, Folder 32)
  - FUNDRAISING MAILING LIST, undated; Series 8 (Box 55, Folder 33)
  - FUNDRAISING, 2002; Series 8 (Box 55, Folder 34)
  - FUNDRAISING, 2000; Series 8 (Box 55, Folder 35)
  - FUNDRAISING, 1999; Series 8 (Box 55, Folder 36)
  - FUNDRAISING, 1998; Series 8 (Box 55, Folder 37)
  - FOUNDATION RESEARCH, undated; Series 8 (Box 55, Folder 38)
  - FOUNDATION CENTER INFORMATION, undated; Series 8 (Box 55, Folder 39)
  - FOUNDATION CENTER BULLETINS, undated; Series 8 (Box 55, Folder 40)